Camouflage before Riichi
That's a Mahjong PREREQUISITE
Hiroyuki,
You've TRANSFORMED
Kid's getting carried away
I won't let my weakness be seen eitherこっちもスキをみせられん(causative passive)
Raaaaychi
So, If I declare Riichi I've got a Mangan, hunh?
No. It would be useless
If I get carried away and declare Riichi, I'll deal into somone's hand調子に乗って振り込めば
And then it's all over
Riichi
And there it is
Ten's in Tenpai too
There it is!
Soga's winning tile
Ehhh?
He won't take it?!?
Why did he let the win pass?
A direct hit off Ten...
would be Mangan with an Ura-Dora
And NOW
Mentanpin Tsumo
Aaaand
any additional Ura-dora?
FUCK YES
A Mangan hand
It can't be
Soga could have won off Tens 7 Pin discard
This is unthinkable
He purposefully waited after passing on my discard
His goal:
To cut down Hiroyuki's pointsひろゆきの点棒を削る
If Hiroyuki falls to just 1000 pointsひろゆきの点が無くなれば
then neither I nor Akagi can declare Tsumo anymore天と赤木はツモ和了り出来なくなる
He decided that was the preferable outcomeその方が良いと判断して
And persistently sought a Tsumo執念でツモ和了りしやがった
Harada is most probably holding a Pinzu (dots) Honisou
So here, should I discard my 7 Sou (bamboo)?
Only a Tatehon hand?(closed multi color)
This won't amount to a Mangan hand
It gets him to Tenpai one turn faster
However
If Hiroyuki igets a 1 or 4 Pin, it might just come out
Looks like Harada's in Tenpai
If that happens then the loss to this side should be largeこちらはロスが多い
If I had discarded a 7 Sou from this hand
He'd be in Tenpai with this 1 Pin draw
The win escaped him?和了り逃しか
Noいや、
It wasn't a mistake at allミスじゃない
hunh?
This hand,この手、
Will soon CHANGE後一手で化ける
A Jyunchan Ryanpeikou???
If he drew something like that it would naturally be a DEMONIC drawそんな牌引いてきたらまさに鬼ヅモだ
My god...
H-he DREW IT
So, now they change
This is badまずい
Ten's discards show he's got a certainly got a large hand天側の捨て牌。確実に大物の手が入っとる
Alright!
Ipeikou Tsumo with 2 Dora
A Mangan win
Hiroyuki,ひろゆき、
I'm sorry悪いな
Let me do what looks crazyここは無茶させてもらう
I've had a PREMONITION予感がする、
A pounding in the earth地の鼓動、
This DRAGONこの龍
Hidden in the earth地に潜らせる
Kan
His hand's a messめちゃくちゃだ
His chance for either Jyunchan or Ryanpeiko just disappeared!これでジュンチャンも二盃口も消えた、
Why?なぜ？
Bakutsu is without doubt in Tenpai阿久津は間違いなく聴牌、
If he wins he could take out the East teamこのままだと間違いなく東が討ち取られる
yee gods
A typical slow SuuAnKou
Is it no use at all?駄目か？
Kan
THE DRAGON HAS PARTED THE EARTH龍が地を割った
Tsumo
SuuAnKou
HE DID IT
This SuuAnKou lowers Akagi's points to 8000
but the other two are OUT AT ONE STROKE
The path to that SuuAnKou was narror and treacherousあの手牌から四暗刻への道のりはあまりに細く険しかった
HOWEVERだが
at the END of that pathそんな道の先にこそ、
Was a way to turn the game around entirely逆転の方法がある
The east as the flow...流れは東
don't they
Aww, it's still okay
Akagi and Hiroyuki are only just BARELY in the game
FUKKIN RETARD!!!アホンダラ！
何ヌルいことぬかしとんじゃワリャ！！
Understand what that win means!さっきの和了でわかったやろ
They put it all on the line捨て身や
It's got NOTHING to do with their fucking POINTS!奴らに点数なんぞ関係ないんじゃ！
Soga僧我さん、
I've already decided what we have to do, Okay?もう手段は選ばんでええ
It's okay, isn't it?ええですな？
As you preferあんたの好きでええよ
More and more this looks like the last round, doesn't itいよいよ最終局面ですね
Ten's SuuAnKou just nowさっきの天の四暗刻で
It lit a fire under those fag's assesやつらのケツに火がついた
They gonna come at us with everything they got捨て身で来るだろう
This isn't a reasonable contest any moreここからは理の勝負じゃない
Eat? Or be eaten?食うか食われるか
It's an instinctual fight本能の戦いだ
Everythingすべて
I'll put my very hert into it己の心に委ねろ
Riichi
It's come
The first Riichi of the roundこの局面でのリーチは
Is first a Mangan hand満貫手
If he draws his tile, it's overツモ和了りされたら終わりだ
Making a quick hand is best here早上がりで流すのが一番良いが
But this hand's a slow one as wellこの手では厳しい
This game doesn't have a "no tenpai penalty"ノーテン罰符が無いのだから、
So I just have to not deal into his hand振り込まないようにするだけ
shitfuckpiss
It wasn't an Itsuu
An end wait on 7 Sou?
Why on earth?
10th Game
South Round 3
Come on!
I'm in Tenpai
If I discard the 5 Pin it's a 1/4 Pin wait
Or if I discard the 3 Pin it's a 2 Pin/White dragon triple wait
Whatever I do my two White Dragons are dora, plus an Iipeikou
If I Riichi it's certainly more than Mangan
There's already two White Dragons discarded...
so my decision is straightforward
Riichi
With such a readable wait
I won't be able to get a direct hit
Naturally the West team won't play it
But I wasn't expecting that from the start
I WILL DRAW IT
I CAN'T BE
FIVE white dragon tiles???白が5枚？
FIVE white dragon tiles?白が5枚？
It's the west team
The West team mixed in an extra White Dragon from the start
But... for what purpose?
Is it insurance?保険か？
At times when you're at a disadvantage, just announcing there's 5 white dragons,自分達が不利な時、白は五枚あることを告げ、
will invalidate the roundその局を無効にするためか
You've got to be kiddingふざけやがって
There's no reason why I have to play along with thisこんなもの認めらるはずがない
BUT, why should I throw away my advantage?だが自分の優位を捨てることはない
If I complete my hand, I win和了れば俺の勝ちだ
If I draw it I WIN
South and North wind tiles?
I can understand him playing around my Riichi
but having a North and South wind floating in your hand so late in the game is unusual
A Kokusi Musou?
Yeah, more and more it's looking that way
But it is amusingしかし愉快だ
張ったところでやつは絶対に出ない白待ちにならざる負えないHe may be in tenpai but I can't lose if he's waiting on a White Dragon that will never come
I've got the other two he's waiting for残り2枚は俺が持っている
Even if Harada thinks there's two remaining原田も2枚あると思えば
It's impossible for him無理をする
And if it's impossible, the chances he deals into my hand increases無理をすれば振り込む確率も高まる
more and more this White Dragonもともとこの白は
原田が自分に理ありと場にそっと混ぜた毒
その毒が皮肉にも
今原田自信に回ってきている
Any moment now...
A SIXTH WHITE DRAGON???6枚目の白？！？
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE FUCKING KIDDINGふざけるな、
Enough with the fucking cheating already無法もいい加減にしろ
Wassamatta?どないしたん
If it doesn't complete your hand get rid of it, or...和了りやないんやったらはよきらんかい。それとも
have you forgotten how to discard?牌のきりかた忘れたんかい
OH, a White Dragon?白か？
Well, then...それや
Ron!ロン！
Kokusi Musou国士無双や
HA HA HA HA HA!
And with this, the game is over!
Stop fucking around,ふざけるな、
I'm not going to accept a game like this!こんな麻雀認められない！
LOOK!みろ！
What I discarded was the SIXTH White Dragon!今きった白は6枚目の白だ
A mess like this...こんなめちゃくちゃな
as if I'd let an illegal move like this go through!無法が通るものか
Illegal?無法か？
But you yourselfだがおどれは
didn't you already accept that Illegal move?その無法を認めとったんちゃうか
If you've got two White Dragons in your hand,手に白を2枚持っとったら、
You drew the 5th White Dragon right after declaring Riichiリーチ直後に引いた白で5枚目や
Thus at that time,おどれはその時から
You should have noticed something off with the game場の異変に気付いとっつたはずや
Why didn't you say anything THEN?なんでその時言わんかったんや
When it suits your purposes自分の理に合う時は
you accept what's illegal無法を認め、
but when it's not to your advantage you go around screaming "illegal, illegal!"都合は悪うなったら無法や無法や騒ぎ出す
That kind of play is simply unacceptableそんなん筋が通らんやろ
No?
Don't you think so, Akagi?そうは思わんか？赤木？
Certainly, you are right.確かにその通りだ
A-Akagi :-(
But Harada,だがな原田、
Despite that, I'm quite sure...それでもやっぱり
you haven't wonお前の和了はねえんだよ
What?
If you accept there are 6 White Dragon tiles6枚の白を認めるとなると
Naturally this game is an exception正に異例の麻雀
And if you accept that exceptionその異例が認められるのなら
You'll have to accept my exception from the rules as well!俺の異例も認めてもらう
Ronロン
Head Bump頭ハネだ
Head bump?
Are you retarded?あほか！
The kid discarded a WHITE DRAGON小僧が今きったのは白や
You're waiting on a 2/5 Sou (bamboo) or a 5 Pin (dots)おどれの待ちは二、五索に五筒やないか
Yes, on the surface表面上はな
HWAAAAAT?
If there's 6 White Dragons...6枚の白が存在しているということは、
There were tiles left out of the gameその分割を食った牌が存在する
Probably three tiles of two typesたぶん3枚しか無い牌が2種
I say that white that Hiroyuki discarded isn't a white at all俺はひろゆきがきった牌を白ではなく、
I say it was destined to be a missing tile I could declare Ron onその割を食った牌と定めロンと言ったのさ
Tiles left out?
Yes
That tile is preciselyその牌はずばり
the 5 Sou (5 bamboo)五索
If you examine the left over tiles in that Mahjong case牌のあまりをまとめてあるあのジャン箱をひっくり返しゃ、
we'll soon know if among the few left over tiles...今割を食って少ない牌が何かすぐわかるだろう
if there's a 5 Sou among them...もし五索なら
you'll accept my head bump俺の頭ハネを認めてもらう
and as it's merely a Tanyao hand断么九だけだから
the game will simply continue局が流れるだけだが
But if there isn't a 5 Sou in that case...もしジャン箱から出た牌が五索やなかったら、
You're out of boundsゴロンや
and the point penalty KNOCKS YOU THE FUCK OUTチョンボでオドレが飛ぶぞ！
If you accept that...それでもええんやったら
I'll agree to it請け負うたるわい
No problem
Akagi,赤木さん、
Please. Don't do it辞めて下さい
The tiles the West team swapped西がすり替えた牌は
Only two types out of 34 in Mahjong麻雀牌三四種の内たった二種
Deciding on just the 5 sou is not a gyamburu you're likely to win!それをたったひとつの五索と断定するのは、あまりに分の悪い勝負
I'm the one that dealt into Harada's hand...俺が原田に振り込んだことでこの場は・・・
Hiro,ひろ
It's gone too farそこはもう通り過ぎたんだよ
Hunh?
I declared a Ron俺は和了を口にした
There's no turning backすでに事態は進行した
My reading that your White should have been a 5 Sou...今お前の白を五索とみた俺の読みが
Is the question at hand成るか否かって問題なのさ
BUT
Hiroyuki,ひろゆき、
Akagi Shigeru himself has said as much赤木しげるがそこまで口にしているんだ
There's no taking it back引き返さねえよ
We can only watch now見守ろうじゃねぇか
Akagi has survived!
What i'm afraid of is who I am dying